<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><labels locale="en">
<label key="1879049230" value="Instance: Unravelling the Thread"/>
<label key="1879049246" value="Instance: Blackwold's Broken"/>
<label key="1879049555" value="Instance: Assault on Archet"/>
<label key="1879049884" value="Instance: Red-pass"/>
<label key="1879049994" value="Instance: Retake Weathertop"/>
<label key="1879051657" value="Instance: Beneath the Greenfields"/>
<label key="1879051764" value="Instance: A Gift for the North"/>
<label key="1879051812" value="Instance: Skorgrím's Tomb"/>
<label key="1879052043" value="Instance: A Burglar's Errand"/>
<label key="1879052053" value="Instance: A Thief in the Night"/>
<label key="1879052341" value="Instance: A Lore-master's Will"/>
<label key="1879052356" value="Instance: A Well-Ordered Mind"/>
<label key="1879052447" value="Instance: A Hunter's Charge"/>
<label key="1879052457" value="Instance: The Hunter's Path"/>
<label key="1879052537" value="Instance: The Unmarked Trail"/>
<label key="1879052622" value="Instance: The Last Refuge"/>
<label key="1879052713" value="Instance: The Gates of Carn Dûm"/>
<label key="1879052956" value="Instance: A Minstrel's Hope"/>
<label key="1879052962" value="Instance: A Song for the Company"/>
<label key="1879053111" value="Instance: A Captain's Standard"/>
<label key="1879054343" value="Instance: The Defence of Trestlebridge"/>
<label key="1879059930" value="Instance: A Champion's Courage"/>
<label key="1879060101" value="Instance: A Guardian's Duty"/>
<label key="1879061103" value="Instance: Assault on Rath Teraig"/>
<label key="1879061120" value="Instance: Rescue by Moonlight"/>
<label key="1879061123" value="Instance: To Avert a War"/>
<label key="1879061565" value="Instance: Othrongroth"/>
<label key="1879062509" value="Instance: Frodo's Burden"/>
<label key="1879063051" value="Instance: To a Ranger's Aid"/>
<label key="1879064582" value="Instance: Carn Dûm"/>
<label key="1879073446" value="Instance: A Road Through the Dark"/>
<label key="1879073497" value="Instance: Jailbreak"/>
<label key="1879073540" value="Instance: The Refuge of Edhelion"/>
<label key="1879073579" value="Instance: Into the Silver Deep"/>
<label key="1879076000" value="Public Instance: Newbie Archet"/>
<label key="1879076001" value="Public Instance: Newbie Thorin's Halls"/>
<label key="1879076779" value="Thorin's Halls"/>
<label key="1879076780" value="Instance: The Hideout"/>
<label key="1879077397" value="Private Instance: Slay the Steward"/>
<label key="1879077455" value="Private Instance: Test"/>
<label key="1879078558" value="Instance: The Great Barrow"/>
<label key="1879078810" value="Instance: Broken Alliance"/>
<label key="1879080018" value="Instance: Garth Agarwen"/>
<label key="1879080858" value="Instance: Thrór's Hammer"/>
<label key="1879081168" value="Instance: Fornost"/>
<label key="1879082285" value="Instance: Urugarth"/>
<label key="1879083265" value="Instance: Fire and Ice"/>
<label key="1879083267" value="Instance: Helegrod"/>
<label key="1879086708" value="Instance: The Blade That Was Broken"/>
<label key="1879087208" value="Instance: The Tomb of Elendil"/>
<label key="1879087637" value="Instance: Barad Gúlaran"/>
<label key="1879088600" value="Private Instance: The Twisted Heart"/>
<label key="1879088646" value="Instance: Thieftaker's Bane"/>
<label key="1879088729" value="Private Instance: Formal Complaint"/>
<label key="1879088741" value="Instance: Oakheart's Might"/>
<label key="1879088953" value="Instance: Amarthiel's Friends"/>
<label key="1879092076" value="Instance: Annuminas Gardens"/>
<label key="1879092077" value="Instance: Annuminas Palace"/>
<label key="1879092078" value="Instance: Annuminas Tomb"/>
<label key="1879092661" value="Instance: The Eye of Angmar"/>
<label key="1879092662" value="Instance: Springing the Trap"/>
<label key="1879093354" value="Instance: Mordirith's Fall"/>
<label key="1879093836" value="Instance: The Bounty Hunter"/>
<label key="1879094769" value="Instance: The Rift of Nûrz Ghâshu"/>
<label key="1879095630" value="Instance: The Rift"/>
<label key="1879095631" value="Instance: The Rift"/>
<label key="1879095632" value="Instance: The Rift"/>
<label key="1879095795" value="Instance: A Trap for the Creature Gollum"/>
<label key="1879095796" value="Instance: Prisoner of the Free Peoples"/>
<label key="1879095797" value="Instance: Mordrambor"/>
<label key="1879095798" value="Instance: Remembrance"/>
<label key="1879101527" value="Instance: Goblin-town Throne Room"/>
<label key="key:620777475:227652915" value="Public Instance: Newbie Archet"/>
<label key="key:620777480:227652915" value="Public Instance: Newbie Thorin's Halls"/>
<label key="key:620777975:227652915" value="Thorin's Halls"/>
<label key="key:620778271:227652915" value="Monster-play Instance: Slay the Steward"/>
<label key="key:620778309:227652915" value="Private Instance: Test"/>
<label key="key:620789385:100438980" value="&lt;u&gt;Barad Gúlaran&lt;/u&gt;&#10;\qHaving obtained all the tools they need to contain a terrible spell, the sorcerers of Angmar retreat to Barad Gúlaran to fulfil the commands of their mistress Amarthiel, while the Rangers of the North seek to hinder them....\q"/>
<label key="key:620789385:109703076" value="&lt;u&gt;A Well-Ordered Mind&lt;/u&gt;&#10;\qDorset Oakes, the son of a lore-master now dead, seeks the knowledge contained in his father's old library and is prepared to hunt for the pages to the catalogue his father had written; however, goblins have been diggin in the caves near the library and may soon break through....\q"/>
<label key="key:620789385:111103604" value="&lt;u&gt;Othrongroth&lt;/u&gt;&#10;\qOthrongroth, the Great Barrow, the oldest and largest of the Edain mounds within the Barrow-downs... And home to some of the most terrifying servants of the Witch-king.\q"/>
<label key="key:620789385:115638206" value="&lt;u&gt;Blackwolds Broken&lt;/u&gt;&#10;\qAmdir's defeat shattered the back of the Blackwolds, but pieces of the mystery remain unsolved....\q"/>
<label key="key:620789385:121343476" value="&lt;u&gt;The Twisted Heart&lt;/u&gt;&#10;\qLongbough the Ent has been roused to anger. The Wood-trolls of the Eavespire are acting in league with a Black Huorn which was once under the Ent's guidance, and Longbough is determined to put an end to their mischief....\q"/>
<label key="key:620789385:125338174" value="&lt;u&gt;Frodo's Burden&lt;/u&gt;&#10;\qI am concerned for Frodo, for he bears a great burden. It is my hope that those whom I have sent to watch over the hobbit will determine if his mind remains strong enough for the task for which he has been chosen....\q"/>
<label key="key:620789385:126153652" value="&lt;u&gt;Helegrod&lt;/u&gt;&#10;\qHelegrod... Once a dwarf-hold in the Misty Mountains, until the coming of a great dragon. Though the dragon has long since perished, and the ice of many long winters has engulfed the ruins, rumours out of the North speak of a terrible shadow returning to the frozen halls....\q"/>
<label key="key:620789385:133737042" value="&lt;u&gt;Haudh Valandil&lt;/u&gt;&#10;\qThe Lords of Umbar, sorcerers trained by Sauron, the great Necromancer, seek to bring terror to Annúminas by raising the long-dead remains of Valandil, third King of Arnor, as a terrible wight. Only the most courageous of the Free Peoples will be able to put an end to their evil deeds. . . .\q"/>
<label key="key:620789385:134938035" value="&lt;u&gt;Barad Tironn&lt;/u&gt;&#10;\qLaerdan, succumbing to the whisperings of Mordrambor, foolishly seeks to confront Amarthiel at Barad Tironn, where she seeks to use the palantír to find Narchuil. The only hope for the Free Peoples is for the palantír to be recovered from her grasp. . . .\q"/>
<label key="key:620789385:140263525" value="&lt;u&gt;Ost Elendil&lt;/u&gt;&#10;\qThe Black Númenóreans in league with Amarthiel have come to Ost Elendil, seeking to establish a foothold in Annúminas, while the Rangers of the North assail the city of their fathers in a desperate attempt to drive them forth.\q"/>
<label key="key:620789385:140499526" value="&lt;u&gt;Thrór's Hammer&lt;/u&gt;&#10;\qDwalin, lord of Thorin's Hall has tasked the Heroes of Eriador with recovering Thrór's hammer from the tomb of Skorgrím, where the Dourhands have enshrined it as a memorial of victory over Durin's Folk....\q"/>
<label key="key:620789385:140499528" value="&lt;u&gt;The Gates of Carn Dûm&lt;/u&gt;&#10;\qUsing the scroll of the Hillmen, a key to the gates of Carn Dûm has been forged. Now the Heroes of Eriador and Lorniel, daughter of Golodir, must pass the gates of the iron fortress and free the Ranger from the clutches of Mordirith, the Steward of Angmar....\q"/>
<label key="key:620789385:14105218" value="&lt;u&gt;To Avert a War&lt;/u&gt;&#10;\qThe Ranger Langlas prepares to mount an effort to rescue the Elf-prince Avorthal from the clutches of the treacherous Dourhands....\q"/>
<label key="key:620789385:145444197" value="&lt;u&gt;A Champion's Courage&lt;/u&gt;&#10;\qMosal-ruk, leader of the Orcs of Ost Cyrn, gathers his strength to crush the Eglain of the Lone-lands and press eastward to Bree-land. Slade Ransford, a champion of the common good, stands ready with his allies to turn back the Orkish war-band....\q"/>
<label key="key:620789385:146692621" value="&lt;u&gt;Carn Dûm&lt;/u&gt;&#10;\qCarn Dûm, the capital of Angmar and the former stronghold of the Witch-king. Angmar's shadow has returned to this city in the form of the False King, Mordirith, Steward of Angmar.\q"/>
<label key="key:620789385:148695075" value="&lt;u&gt;To a Ranger's Aid&lt;/u&gt;&#10;\qAmdir, quickly falling into the shadows of the wraith-world, has slain two of his brethren already and seeks the blood of a third....\q"/>
<label key="key:620789385:148910261" value="&lt;u&gt;Broken Alliance&lt;/u&gt;&#10;\qAfter learning of a plot by Sharkey's Men to forge an alliance with the Orcs encroaching into the northern Bree-fields, the Ranger Saeradan sets into motion a plan to break the alliance before it can be established....\q"/>
<label key="key:620789385:15380674" value="&lt;u&gt;Red-pass&lt;/u&gt;&#10;\qThe Gaunt-lord Ivar spreads corruption through Agamaur, the Red Swamp, raising a host of evil to do the bidding of Angmar....\q"/>
<label key="key:620789385:153962948" value="&lt;u&gt;Retake Weathertop&lt;/u&gt;&#10;\qWeathertop... once a watchtower of the Dúnedain, now a refuge for Orcs. Candaith the Ranger strives to break their foothold in the Weather Hills....\q"/>
<label key="key:620789385:156314804" value="&lt;u&gt;A Formal Complaint&lt;/u&gt;&#10;\qAn attempt to lodge a formal complaint on behalf of the glassblower, Hob Hillbrow, led to a violent encounter with the Chief's Men. The time has come to put the ruffians in their place....\q"/>
<label key="key:620789385:156549379" value="&lt;u&gt;Prisoner of the Free Peoples&lt;/u&gt;&#10;\qThe pages of Sara Oakheart's journal uncovered the way into the ruins of Delossad, once called Sithad in brighter days. The search for Narchuil has led here, but to what end? What have these ragged stones seen. . . ?\q"/>
<label key="key:620789385:159616245" value="&lt;u&gt;The Defence of Trestlebridge&lt;/u&gt;&#10;\qThe little town of Trestlebridge is all that stands between the Orcs of Angmar and Bree-land to the south. Halbarad, Ranger of the North, gathers heroes to help defend Trestlebridge from the approaching onslaught....\q"/>
<label key="key:620789385:159881209" value="&lt;u&gt;A Guardian's Duty&lt;/u&gt;&#10;\qThe town of Trestlebridge is under siege by by Orcs out of Angmar. One of the guardians of Trestlebridge, Severin Wheeler, has assembled the townsfolk and their southern allies to defend the town against the marauding hordes....\q"/>
<label key="key:620789385:161760089" value="&lt;u&gt;A Song for the Company&lt;/u&gt;&#10;\qHoping for some new material with which to compose a song, the minstrel Piper Prescott has recruited young blood to aid the hobbit Leland Underhill retrieve some goods stolen from him by the brigands encamped throughout Bree-land....\q"/>
<label key="key:620789385:17941376" value="&lt;u&gt;Springing the Trap&lt;/u&gt;&#10;\qThe Rangers of the North have learned that Mordrambor, a Black Númenórean deep in the counsels of Amarthiel, is travelling to Haudh Elendil with a small retinue. Hoping to sieze Mordrambor, the Rangers stage an ambush. . . .\q"/>
<label key="key:620789385:179694421" value="&lt;u&gt;A Minstrel's Hope&lt;/u&gt;&#10;\qSeveral citizens of the besieged town of Trestlebridge have taken refuge in nearby caves, hoping to wait out the siege, but the Orcs have become aware of the townsfolk's hiding place. It is up to the minstrel Leigh Putnam and her friends to warn them....\q"/>
<label key="key:620789385:181888370" value="&lt;u&gt;A Road Through the Dark&lt;/u&gt;&#10;\qA distressing letter speaks of troubles beyond the Shire, leading a hobbit to take the long road to Archet, fraught with danger....\q"/>
<label key="key:620789385:183124382" value="&lt;u&gt;The Blade That Was Broken&lt;/u&gt;&#10;\qThe time of Isildur's Heir is at hand. With the recovery of the last Silithar, Elrond has commanded that the light of Narsil, which cut the One Ring from the hand of Sauron, be renewed and rekindled as Anduril, the Flame of the West....\q"/>
<label key="key:620789385:185499447" value="&lt;u&gt;Assault on Rath Teraig&lt;/u&gt;&#10;\qThe combined forces of Lord Dwalin of Thorin's Hall and Dorongúr Whitethorn of Duillond prepare to march upon the goblin-army at Rath Teraig....\q"/>
<label key="key:620789385:192939781" value="&lt;u&gt;The Last Refuge&lt;/u&gt;&#10;\qSkorgrím's Dourhands have taken refuge from the wrath of Durin's Folk within an ancient dwarf-hold high in the passes of the Misty Mountains. There, they plot their return, unless an end can be put to their scheming once and for all....\q"/>
<label key="key:620789385:196352805" value="&lt;u&gt;Thief-taker's Bane&lt;/u&gt;&#10;\qA simple quest to recover ancient Dúnedain relics from the hands of the grave-robbers who stole them has gone terribly awry. The thieves will not allow the Rangers and their allies to take their treasures from them so easily....\q"/>
<label key="key:620789385:197377268" value="&lt;u&gt;A Thief in the Night&lt;/u&gt;&#10;\qThe hobbit-burglar Atherol Took has learned that some of the Big Folk who have been causing trouble in the Southfarthing of the Shire are planning to sneak onto Farmer Maggot's land and steal his mushrooms. Atherol has no intention of allowing hobbit-mushrooms to be stolen by Men....\q"/>
<label key="key:620789385:19890162" value="&lt;u&gt;Into the Silver Deep&lt;/u&gt;&#10;\qThorin Oakenshield prepares to depart for the Lonely Mountain, and an assembly is called to bid his Company good fortune....\q"/>
<label key="key:620789385:202833532" value="&lt;u&gt;The Unmarked Trail&lt;/u&gt;&#10;\qAn ancient evil, a corruption of the very nature of Middle-earth, threatens to spread its vile poison throughout the Trollshaws. This evil must be thwarted before it can be brought to bear against the hidden vale of Rivendell.\q"/>
<label key="key:620789385:205906597" value="&lt;u&gt;Remembrance&lt;/u&gt;&#10;\qToo many of the Dúnedain have fallen to the ravages of one who is their distant kinsman. There is a time for mourning, but is this that time, when the Champion of Angmar might secure her ring, Narchuil. . . ?\q"/>
<label key="key:620789385:21619996" value="&lt;u&gt;A Lore-master's Will&lt;/u&gt;&#10;\qThe Elf-loremaster Isferon received a gift from his friend Berenon before he passed over the Sea, but the gift is wrapped in a riddle. Before the gift can be revealed Berenon's puzzle must be solved....\q"/>
<label key="key:620789385:216223236" value="&lt;u&gt;A Burglar's Errand&lt;/u&gt;&#10;\qMedhrod, a legendary sword once wielded by a great hero who helped keep the Great East Road clear of threats, has been stolen by the half-orcs of Naerost, leading Palma Brownlock, a hobbit-burglar of no small reputation, to gather allies to recover it....\q"/>
<label key="key:620789385:230006418" value="&lt;u&gt;The Bounty Hunter&lt;/u&gt;&#10;\qBasil Gummidge hired adventurers from throughout Eriador to bring the ruffians and tomb-robbers of Evendim to justice, but now a notorious tomb-robber, Cuthbert Sprunt, has placed a bounty upon the arbiter's own hunters....\q"/>
<label key="key:620789385:230273044" value="&lt;u&gt;Oakheart's Might&lt;/u&gt;&#10;\qA mysterious note from the strange Sara Oakheart bade the heroes who saved her meet her at the gates of Barad Gúlaran, the ancient retreat of the Witch-king of Angmar. Seeking an answer to the mystery of the old woman, Golodir assents....\q"/>
<label key="key:620789385:233393896" value="&lt;u&gt;The Hunter's Path&lt;/u&gt;&#10;\qAn terrible and vicious wolf called Yellowfang stalks through the Old Forest, often ambushing travellers upon the Great East Road. The accomplished huntress Gytha Lainey is resolved to ridding the Forest of this savage threat....\q"/>
<label key="key:620789385:240047395" value="&lt;u&gt;Glinghant&lt;/u&gt;&#10;\qGlinghant, the gardens of Annúminas -- once a place of great beauty, now overgrown and fallen into ruin. The stagnant of waters of the gardens have become corrupted by the fell spirits of Angmar, and evil Men do their bidding. . . .\q"/>
<label key="key:620789385:244759253" value="&lt;u&gt;Amarthiel's Hope&lt;/u&gt;&#10;\qSuspecting that Amarthiel, the champion of Angmar, has come to Annúminas -- a suspicion supported by the warning of the Elf Laerdan -- the Rangers of the North prepare to infiltrate the ruined city and put an end to her evil plans....\q"/>
<label key="key:620789385:246990133" value="&lt;u&gt;A Hunter's Charge&lt;/u&gt;&#10;\qAfter receiving word of a pack of Wargs making their way into the Shire, land of the hobbits, the huntress Gytha Lainey has recruited the best hunters to track and slay the evil Wargs before they can harm any of the Shire-folk....\q"/>
<label key="key:620789385:249034316" value="&lt;u&gt;The Tomb of Elendil&lt;/u&gt;&#10;\qRespect, the one thing Gwindeth desired most, has earned passage into the tomb of Elendil, the resting place of the last Silithar. But with the lowering of the floods, robbers and thieves have taken the opportunity to plunder the tomb....\q"/>
<label key="key:620789385:253214051" value="&lt;u&gt;Unravelling the Thread&lt;/u&gt;&#10;\qStrider and the Rangers pursue their fallen brother Amdir to the Blackwolds' camp, but not all is as it seems....\q"/>
<label key="key:620789385:264040680" value="&lt;u&gt;Fire and Ice&lt;/u&gt;&#10;\qElrond Halfelven fears that the remaining Nazgûl has enlisted the aid of the Gaunt-lord Drugoth to instill a fell spirit into the frozen corpse of the ancient Dragon Thorog and raise the beast once more as a wight. Little time remains to stop their evil plans.\q"/>
<label key="key:620789385:268174811" value="&lt;u&gt;Jailbreak&lt;/u&gt;&#10;\qA chance encounter with brigands upon the road leads to captivity, but rescue may not be far away....\q"/>
<label key="key:620789385:31055636" value="&lt;u&gt;Skorgrím's Tomb&lt;/u&gt;&#10;\qLord Dwalin's investigation has uncovered the treachery of the Dourhands. While Durin's Folk prepare to drive the Dourhands from Thorin's Hall, Dwalin gathers his forces to stop a darker threat....\q"/>
<label key="key:620789385:41063900" value="&lt;u&gt;Mordirith's Fall&lt;/u&gt;&#10;\qHeartened by the gift of Dúnachar from Elrond of Rivendell, Golodir prepares to assail Carn Dûm and drive the sword into the unseen heart of Mordirith, the murderous Steward of Angmar. Courage may bring hope, but a thirst for vengeance could spell doom. . . .\q"/>
<label key="key:620789385:41766322" value="&lt;u&gt;Mordrambor&lt;/u&gt;&#10;\qThe time has come. Angered by Mordrambor's treacherous betrayal of Laerdan, the Ranger Calenglad is determined to confront the Black Númenórean and learn where Narchuil, the ring of Amarthiel, resides. . . .\q"/>
<label key="key:620789385:46644709" value="&lt;u&gt;Goblin-town Throne Room&lt;/u&gt;&#10;\qIn the darkest depths of Goblin-town, at the heart of the goblin kingdom, teeming with the vile breed, lay the throne room of the Great Goblin. Long have the inhabitants of Goblin-town been leaderless, but as the Shadow in the East grows, calling its minions to arms, a new leader has taken the mantle of the Great Goblin....\q"/>
<label key="key:620789385:49157380" value="&lt;u&gt;Rescue by Moonlight&lt;/u&gt;&#10;\qAvorthal had been moved from the Dourhand encampment to a ship preparing to depart for an unknown port in the North. His rescue is paramount to maintaining peace in Ered Luin....\q"/>
<label key="key:620789385:66867572" value="&lt;u&gt;Assault on Archet&lt;/u&gt;&#10;\qÉogan and the Blackwolds renew their efforts to secure Mundo Sackville-Baggins for the ominous Black Riders....\q"/>
<label key="key:620789385:72783710" value="&lt;u&gt;Garth Agarwen&lt;/u&gt;&#10;\qGarth Agarwen . . . The ruins of an ancient fortress of Rhudaur, now overrun by corrupted nature and a vile necromantic power out of Angmar. The most terrible power still remains to be confronted.\q"/>
<label key="key:620789385:79092434" value="&lt;u&gt;Beneath the Greenfields&lt;/u&gt;&#10;\qThe goblins of Mount Gram have never forgotten their defeat at the hands of the Shire-folk, and revenge has brought them hither once more....\q"/>
<label key="key:620789385:85106791" value="&lt;u&gt;Othrongroth&lt;/u&gt;&#10;\qAn unholy alliance is forged within the depths of Othrongroth, the Great Barrow, a sinister pact which could spell doom for Eriador....\q"/>
<label key="key:620789385:86837640" value="&lt;u&gt;A Gift for the North&lt;/u&gt;&#10;\qThe Stone-troll of Rushock Bog... a terrible legend stalks the fens, enraged by the dwarves who seek to capture it....\q"/>
<label key="key:620789385:96611396" value="&lt;u&gt;A Captain's Standard&lt;/u&gt;&#10;\qDwarves of the Dourhand house have taken refuge in the ruins of Ost Galumar, not far from the mines of Othrikar, stirring the Longbeards of Othrikar to action. Jarl Copperbrace recruits the bravest of the brave to deal with the threat of the Dourhands....\q"/>
<label key="key:620789385:97841122" value="&lt;u&gt;The Refuge of Edhelion&lt;/u&gt;&#10;\qThe refuge of Edhelion has come under attack by dwarves and goblins led by the cruel Skorgrím Dourhand....\q"/>
<label key="key:620789385:99352885" value="&lt;u&gt;A Trap for the Creature&lt;/u&gt;&#10;\qWistan, a hunter in Tâl Bruinen, believes a trap can be set for the skulking creature which has terrorized the scattered inhabitants remaining in the region. Nevertheless, the creature has been a wary and cunning opponent. . . .\q"/>
</labels>
